Lekki Gardens Phase II, Lagos State, Nigeria. hello.thankgodokoro@gmail.com 08162680095

Okoro E.M ThankGod

Product Designer/ Web Developer

SKILLS

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustration
- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Corel Draw
- Adobe Premiere Pro Joomla
- Excellent work ethic
- WordPress
- HTML5
- CSS3
- PHP
- Javascript
- React JS
- MERN Stack
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- Bootstrap
- Vue
- Angular
- UI/UX Design
- Good communication skills and Good Relationship Management.

Innovative Web Developer with six years of experience in website design and Product Designer. A skilled professional who brings a masterful approach to web presence planning, launch, and management. Consistently handled complex aspects of marketin g, sof are development, and SEO.

Detailed understanding of languages such as HTML, CSS, Java, and other intricate programming languages as well as scripting languages as MySQL JavaScript, and front and back-end web development to optimie online presence.

EXPERIENCE

iVerify.ng, Lagos — FullStack Developer

2021-2022

- Developing front end website architecture.
- Designing user interactions on web pages.
- Developing back-end website applications.
- Creating servers and databases for functionality.
- Ensuring cross-platform optimization for mobile phones.
- Product Designer
- Ensuring responsiveness of applications.
- Working alongside graphic designers for web design features.

iBrand Africa LTD, Port Harcourt— I.T Consultant

2018-2020

- Adjusted soft are parameters to boost performance and incorporate new features.
- Developed and implemented policies, procedures, training, and development for network resource administration, appopri te use, and disaster recovery.
- Made recommendations and peormed upgrades, assisssting businesses in technology planning aligned with growth projections.
- Managed and approved content for design for the company, maintain the company's online presence, run and manage the company's public image and branding.

EDUCATION

Ojims College, Port Harcourt — West Africa Examination Council (WAEC)

2006-2012

Community Primary School, Elekahia, Port Harcourt — First School Leaving Certificate (FSLC)

1999-2005

University of Port Harcourt — BSC in progress

HOBBIES:

- Traveling
- Listening to Music
- Swimming

Kel Technologies LTD, Port Harcourt— *Creative/IT Manager*

2017-2018

- Generated content design for the company.
- Maintained the company's online presence by regularly posting content on social media.
- Increased website and social media traffic by 45% by creaeating dynamic graphics and pieces.
- Developed original content through social listening and independent sources.
- Collaborated with SEO and content team to produce website content.
- Conducted extensive research to provide factual statistics for articles, blogs, and landing pages.
- Ran and managed the company's e-commerce website.

iBrand Africa, Port Harcourt — *Graphic/Web(CMS) Designer, Social Media Publicist, Creative Dire or*

2016 - 2017

- Determined coding requirements for site creation, including e-commerce capability, security, and specialized scripts.
- Mapped user journey end-to-end using information achiecture diagrams, user flows, wireframes, and paper and interracte prototypes.
- Increased website security by keeping software up to date, using and safeguarding strong passwords, and monitoring the website for security vulnerabilities.
- Developed site content and graphics by coordinating copywriting, and designing images, icons, banners, and enhancements.
- Handled content generation or banding for companies, graphics design (Company profiles, Billboard designs, Magazines, Brochures. Etc). Website design and maintenance for the company and clients.
- Developed artistic visual products while working within defined technical constraints.

Virtual Integrated Concept, Port Harcourt— *Computer Operator*

2014 - 2015

- Operated and maintained the 5D ride machine.
- Monitored systems in operation and input ommands to troubleshoot specific areas.
- Generated monthly reports covering details about data, system operation, and eor monitoring.
- Kept soft are licenses current for all computers and mobile devices.
- Managed program errors with an analyti al approach focused on troubleshootin, diagnosing, and resolving each problem.

Cross River Broadcasting Corpoa ationCalabar— *Video Editor*

JUNE - DECEMBER 2014

- Edited programs(jingles, announcements, etc.) to be aired.
- Edited videos for digital distribution by managing aphics, sound, music mix, and color correction.
- Curated and handled creatile dirrectionor video ontent.